[{"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " what are you guys doing up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " oh, we wanted to finish the crossword before we went to bed. hey, do you know a six-letter word for red?", "answer": "  dark red.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " yeah, i think that's wrong, but there's a connect the dots in here for you later.  hey, how about maroon?", "answer": "  yes, you are so smart!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " aww, you guys are so cute!", "answer": " i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " y'know, i love doing crossword puzzles with you honey!", "answer": " aww, me too. now let's finish this and go to bed.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " okay! there's only one left, three letter word, not dog but\u009a", "answer": " cat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " yes! you are so smart!  i love you.", "answer": " i love you too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": "  uhh, we still need a tip.", "answer": " all right. hold on.  i got it. nickel!  how much more do we need?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " a couple of bucks.", "answer": " okay, dime!  you guys should probably keep talking; this could take a while.  oh no, wait! look it! whoa!  oh my god, this is a police badge!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " wow!", "answer": " oh that's so cool! why would a cop come in here though? they don't serve donuts.  y'know what actually, could you discover the badge again? i think i can come up with something better than that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " phoebe, i bet somebody's missing that badge.", "answer": " yeah, i should probably take it back. ooh, but you know what? while i'm at the police station, i could check their ten most wanted lists because my friend fritzy has been like number 11 forever, so this could be her year!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": "  hey, you guys!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " hey joey!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": "  hey. that uh, that my sweatshirt?", "answer": " oh yes, it is. i'm sorry i borrowed it, i was cold. i hope its okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " well uh, it's just that uh, y'know if-if you're gonna be wearing someone's sweatshirt shouldn't it be your boyfriends--and i\u0092m not him.", "answer": " i'm sorry, i'll give it back to you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " no-no! no! i mean it's gonna be all smelling like monica!", "answer": " are you saying i smell bad?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " what's with him?", "answer": " oh, y'know what? the last time joey went to a meadow, his mother was shot by a hunter.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": "  ugh!", "answer": "  yeah, i still don't know.  i'm sorry i just wanna make sure that i bought the right couch. i need a couch that says, \"kids welcome here.\" but that also says,  \"come here to me!\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " what?! you say that to kids?!!", "answer": " no! no! no! the \"come here to me\" is y'know for the ladies.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " ross, honey, it's a nice couch. it's not a magic couch.", "answer": " you picked a great couch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " yeah. could you just sign right here please?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " oh, sure. whoa-whoa, what's this? the delivery charge is almost as much as the couch!", "answer": " wait! no, that's ridiculous. come on, he lives three blocks away!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " yeah!   are you kiddin'?", "answer": " oh, come on it's only three blocks! and-and, it's not very heavy, try it! come on! come on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": "  oh. oh! i can do it!", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " you two are really gonna enjoy that couch.", "answer": " oh yeah, we're uh, yeah we're not together.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " ross!", "answer": " what's that supposed to mean?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " ross!", "answer": " well you, her, i mean, she's very\u009ay'know. and you're like\u009ay'know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " not that it's any of your business, but we did go out.", "answer": " really? you two?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " yeah! rach?", "answer": " come on, i don't really want to be doing this right now. i am carrying a very heavy couch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " then tell him quickly.", "answer": "  fine!  we went out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " not only did we go out, we did it 298 times!", "answer": " ross!! oh my--ugh!! you kept count?! you are such a loser!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " oh. oh! ma'am? excuse me, ma'am? the smoking woman: yes?", "answer": " you can't put your cigarette out on a tree! the smoking woman: yeah i can, it worked real well.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " no but you shouldn't! don't ever do that again. the smoking woman: i won't!  until i have my next cigarette.", "answer": " hold it!  n.y.p.d! freeze punk! the smoking woman: what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " yeah that's right you are so busted.  book 'em. the smoking woman: who are you talking too?", "answer": " save it red! unless you wanna spend the night in the slammer, you apologize to the tree. the smoking woman: i am not going to apologize to a tree!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " you apologize to the tree right now or i am calling for backup.   backup! backup!! the smoking woman: i-i'm sorry! sorry.", "answer": " okay, cancel backup! cancel backup!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " ross, didn't you say that there was an elevator in here?", "answer": " uhh, yes i did but there isn't. okay, here we go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " okay, y'know what? there is no more left, left!", "answer": " oh okay, lift it straight up over your head! straight up over your head! you can do it! you can do it!  okay. you got", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " good-good-good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " \u009aso this guy was all  and i'm all, buffay, homicide.  it was just so cool!", "answer": "  phoebe, you were supposed to take that back!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " i know but i'm having so much fun doing good deeds.", "answer": " okay, but impersonating a police officer is a serious thing. you could get arrested.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": "  hey.", "answer": "  hey!  oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " hi, joe.", "answer": " yeah, i didn\u0092t know you guys were going to be here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": "  what?! why?!", "answer": " what is going on with you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " nothing!", "answer": " oh, come on! you've been acting strange all day!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa-what-what if martin luther king had said that?  i kinda have a dream! i don\u0092t want to talk about it.", "answer": " well, it involved monica.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " don't worry, there wasn't any sex in it or anything. i haven't dreamt about her like that since i found out about you two--ish.", "answer": " what was the dream about?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " well, okay. you were my girlfriend and we were doing the crossword puzzle. y'know like you guys were doing last night. so, that's it. i'm in love with monica and i'll be moving out.", "answer": " wait, joey! joey! that doesn\u0092t mean that-that you're in love with me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " it-it doesn\u0092t?", "answer": " no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " no, it can mean anything. like uh, all of the sudden you're jealous because i've become the apartment stud.", "answer": " that kinda sounds like your dream dude.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " or, it could mean that-that you saw chandler and me together and we y'know were being close and stuff and then you just want to have that with someone too.", "answer": " in the dream i did enjoy the closeness.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " um-hmm.", "answer": " joey, look, are you attracted to monica? right here, right now, are you attracted to her?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": "  not really.", "answer": " well there you have it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " well sure! i'm just wearing sweats!  but that's good that you're not in love with me, because you just want a girlfriend!", "answer": " no, i don't think it's just about just getting a girlfriend. y'know? i mean, yeah, i can get a girlfriend! yeah, we could sit in the chair and do crosswords, but y'know are we ever going to have y'know the closeness like-like you guys have?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " well y'know, monica and i were friends before we started dating. so maybe-maybe that's it?", "answer": " friends first? that's interesting.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " you become friends after?", "answer": " no, never done that either.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": "  hey, umm, do you guys have that tape measure?", "answer": " oh yeah, it's actually in my bedroom.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": "  what's up joey?", "answer": "  how you doin'?  commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " excuse me, is this your car?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " well i don't think it's very nice of you to park here, y'know you're blocking the entrance.", "answer": " don't worry about it. it's not a problem.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": "  so am i!", "answer": " ohh, no.  oh okay, so you're a cop which means you can park anywhere, 'cause i know that 'cause i'm a cop too. so, all right, keep up the good work. 10-4.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": "  hey, wait a second! so wait, what precinct are you with?", "answer": " i-i'm with the umm, the 57th.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " oh, i know a guy in homicide up there.", "answer": " i'm in vice. yeah, in fact i'm undercover right now. i'm a whore.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " who-who else is in vice up there?", "answer": " umm, do you know, umm sipowicz?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " sipowicz? no, i don't think so.", "answer": " yeah, big guy, kinda bald.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " no, i don't know him.", "answer": "  don\u0092t try to call him or anything, 'cause he's not there, he's out. his umm, his partner just died.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " wow umm, tell sipowicz i'm real sorry for his loss.", "answer": " i-i sure will, take care.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": "  hey by the way, i'm sure sipowicz is gonna be all right. i heard that kid from silver spoons is really good.  and where did you find my badge?", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " hey! joey, would you mind giving me and ross a hand moving his couch?", "answer": " oh, i'd love too, but i got acting class. but y'know what? i guess i can blow that off,  for you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " thanks!", "answer": " uh, hey, rach let me ask you something. uh, i was just over there talking to monica and chandler, boy they are really tight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " i know.", "answer": " yeah that's not such a bad situation they got going over there. i'm thinking of getting me one of those.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " what's up joe?", "answer": " well, the reason i think monica and chandler are so great\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " \u009ais because they were friends first. y'know? so i asked myself, \"who are my friends?\" you and phoebe, and i saw you first. so\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": "  what are you saying?", "answer": " i'm saying maybe you and i crank it up a notch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " y'know honey, umm, as uh, as flattered as i am that uh, you saw me first, uhh, i just, i-i don't think we should be cranking anything up.", "answer": " i'll treat you real nice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": "  yeah, well, y'know umm\u009a no honey, listen i think it's a great idea to become friends with someone before you date them, but i think the way you do it is y'know you meet someone, become their friend, build a foundation, then you ask them out on a date. don't hit on your existing friends!", "answer": " won't-won't that take longer?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " yeah. yeah. oh, but once you find it, ohh it's so worth the wait.", "answer": " yeah. i understand. i understand.  man, i wish i saw phoebe first!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " come here to me. no-no, you come here to me.", "answer": "  hey ross! i brought reinforcements.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " oh great! what, you brought joey?", "answer": " well, i brought the next best thing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " chandler?! you brought chandler?! the next best thing would be monica!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " y'know, i would be offended, but monica is freakishly strong, so\u009a", "answer": " look, i-i drew a sketch about how we're gonna do it.  okay rach,  that's you. that's the couch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " oh, that's me.", "answer": " wow! you certainly think a lot of yourself.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " no! that's-that's my arm!", "answer": "  oh, i see. i thought you just really, really liked your new couch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " okay!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " all right, ready?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " turn.", "answer": "  okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " okay, i don't think we can turn anymore!", "answer": " ross, i don't, i just don't think it's going to fit.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " oh yeah it will! come on, up! up-up-up! up! yes! here we go! pivot!  pivot! piv-ot! piv-et!! piv-ett!!! piv-et!", "answer": " shut up! shut up! shut up!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " okay, i don't think it's going to pivot anymore. chandler and rachel: you think?!", "answer": " all right, let's uh, let's bring it back down and-and try again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " okay, yeah, i think it's really stuck now.", "answer": " i can't believe that didn't work!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " i know, me neither! i mean, you had a sketch!", "answer": " oh, y'know, what did you mean when you said pivot?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey! how's it going? did you make any new friends?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": "  hey, whoa-whoa! what's she like?", "answer": " uhh, well, she's\u009areally good in bed.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " joey, i thought you were gonna try to be friends first!", "answer": "  well look, hey, it's all your fault!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " what?! why?!", "answer": " well because you didn't give me advice! no! you gave me a pickup line! as soon as i told her i wanted to y'know, build a foundation and be friends first. i suddenly, through no fault of my own, became irresistible to her!  and her roommate!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " what about the closeness?", "answer": " closeness-shmoshness! there was three of us for crying out loud!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": "  all right! hey, who wants pizza?!", "answer": " ooh, i do! i do! i do!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " who is it?", "answer": " n.y.p.d!! phoebe and joey: oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " i'm looking for phoebe buffay!", "answer": " ooh, god, it's him! it's that cop! god, i can't believe it! he found me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " oh my god, phoebe, are you gonna go to jail?!", "answer": " well, if i'm going down, i'm taking you  with me.  harboring a fugitive? that's one to three years minimum. good luck chandler.  okay, you can arrest me. fine. but you'll never make it stick and you know it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " yeah, but i kinda don't have a choice, it's my job. i mean, you understand right?", "answer": " yep! as long as you understand that i'm going to call my lawyer and once he puts you on the stand he'll make you look like a fool. a fool!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " i don't like looking foolish. y'know what? maybe uh, i don't arrest you today. maybe i came by and you weren't here.", "answer": " i would love it if i weren't here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " okay, so since umm, you're not going to jail tonight i was wondering if you would like to go to dinner with", "answer": " me?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " yeah. ever since you flashed my badge at me, i kinda can't stop thinking about you. you're the prettiest, fake undercover whore i've ever seen. chandler and joey: nice!", "answer": " wow! i didn't see that coming! you're-you're asking me out!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " yeah. i mean, i coulda done it better, but these people keep staring at me.", "answer": " umm, yeah, i'd like to go out with you officer\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " gary.", "answer": " gary.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " okay, so it's a date.", "answer": " yeah! so--ooh, i gotta ask you though. how did you know where to find me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " well you're fingerprints were all over my badge so i just ran it through the computer and this was listed as your last known address so i just checked it out.", "answer": " ohh, impressive.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " not as impressive as you. i gotta tell you, i looked at your record and you've done some pretty weird stuff.", "answer": " yeah, we'll talk at dinner.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " okay.  so i'll come by in a couple hours and pick you up?", "answer": " all right, i can't wait!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " you wanna return this couch?  it's cut in half!", "answer": " that's what i'm telling you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " did you cut this couch in half?", "answer": " this couch, is cut in half! i would like to exchange it for one that is not cut in half!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " you're telling me this couch was delivered to you like this?!", "answer": " look, i am a reasonable man. i will accept store credit.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " i'll give you store credit in the amount of four dollars.", "answer": "  i take it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}]